Guide to the Amos Niven Wilder and Wilder Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Wiggin and Dana LLP Records, 1910-2012; Series X
  - Thornton Wilder collected materials, 1922–2010
    - Materials from "Box 1"
      - Thornton Wilder collected materials (from square box potentially from 2014 Wiggin and Dana)
        - The Skin of Our Teeth programs, 1997–2007 (Box 389, Folder 5207-5208)
        - Heaven's My Destination programs, 2008–2009 (Box 389, Folder 5209)
        - The Thornton Wilder Society Newsletters, 2004–2011 (Box 395, Folder 5223-5224)
        - First International Thornton Wilder Conference, 2008 October (Box 389, Folder 5210-5211)
        - Thornton Wilder postage stamp and centennial celebration materials, 1996–1997 (Box 389, Folder 5212-5214)
        - Thornton Wilder postage stamp materials, 1995–2007 (Box 390, Folder 5215-5218)
          "Wilder in the Twenty- first Century" conference held at the College of New Jersey.
        - Isabel Wilder's address rolodex, undated (Box 425)
          Includes photographs, clippings, and ephemera.
      - "The Bible Open and Closed" framed poster, 2003 October 23 (Box 400)
      - Framed photograph of Amos N. Wilder preaching, circa 1960 (Box 399)
- Restricted Fragile Materials, 1866–1970; Series XI
  - Amos Parker Wilder
    - Clippings, 1909–1921 (Box 415, Folder 5313)
    - Editorials, 1903–1928 (Box 415, Folder 5314-5317)
    - New Haven Journal- Courier Clippings, 1921–1926 (Box 415, Folder 5318-5319)
    - New Haven Journal- Courier materials, 1923–1960 (Box 415, Folder 5320)
    - New Haven Palladium notes and clippings, undated (Box 415, Folder 5321)
    - Wisconsin State Journal clippings, 1960 (Box 415, Folder 5322)
    - Editorial, circa 1920 (Box 415, Folder 5323)
    - Notes and speeches, 1893–1970 (Box 415, Folder 5324)
    - Yale Alumni Weekly, 1901–1916 (Box 415, Folder 5325)
    - Yale speeches and clippings, 1901–1920 (Box 415, Folder 5326)
    - China and Hong Kong clippings, 1906–1936 (Box 415, Folder 5327)
    - Clippings notebook (folder 2 of 2), circa 1910 (Box 415, Folder 5328)
    - Clippings scrapbook (folder 2 of 2), 1912–1913 (Box 415, Folder 5329)
    - International periodicals, 1909–1935 (Box 415, Folder 5330)
    - State Department correspondence, 1908–1930 (Box 415, Folder 5331)
    - Yale in China materials, 1916–1968 (Box 415, Folder 5332)
    - Editorial in the Yali Quarterly, 1925 (Box 415, Folder 5333)
    - Lincoln, Allen B., 1932–1966 (Box 416, Folder 5334)
    - General Correspondence, I- Z, 1913–1935 (Box 416, Folder 5335)
    - Stewart, George, 1921–1925 (Box 416, Folder 5336)
    - Wilder, Amos Lincoln (1 folder out of 3), 1866–1926 (Box 416, Folder 5337)
    - Wilder, Amos Niven (includes 5 out of 8 folders), 1911–1930 (Box 416, Folder 5338-5342)
    - Wilder children, circa 1910 (Box 416, Folder 5343)
    - Amos and Charlotte Potter Wilder clippings, undated (Box 416, Folder 5344)
  - Isabella Wilder
    - Amos P. Wilder condolence letters, circa 1936 (Box 416, Folder 5345-5346)
    - Wilder, Amos Niven and Catharine (3 of 10 folders), 1917–1946 (Box 416, Folder 5347-5351)
    - Amos P. Wilder memorial materials, 1936–1937 (Box 416, Folder 5352)
    - Clippings and printed poems, 1865–1932 (Box 416, Folder 5353)
    - Niven, Elizabeth Lewis (2 folders), 1916–1923 (Box 416, Folder 5354-5355)
    - Niven, Thornton MacNess, 1894–1972 (Box 416, Folder 5356)
    - Todd family clippings, circa 1894 (Box 416, Folder 5357)
  - Amos N. Wilder
    - Family member related clippings, 1933–1982 (Box 416, Folder 5358)
    - Hello Dolly clippings, correspondence, and ephemera (folder 1 of 4), 1964–1965 (Box 416, Folder 5359)
    - Wilder family clippings, circa 1980 (Box 416, Folder 5360-5361)
    - Wilder, Isabella obituary clipping, 1946 (Box 416, Folder 5362)
    - Wilder, Thornton clippings (6 of 8 folders), 1974 (Box 416, Folder 5363-5367)
    - Wilder, Thornton German materials, 1952–1977 (Box 416, Folder 5368)
    - Wilder, Thornton, The Eighth Day clippings, 1967 (Box 416, Folder 5369)
    - Clippings (folders 5 of 6), circa 1918-1980 (Box 416, Folder 5370-5374)
    - Ehrlich, Virginia and Daniels, Mabel obituary clippings, speech typescript, and materials, 1968–1973 (Box 416, Folder 5375)
    - North Conway materials (folder 3 of 3), 1932–1984 (Box 416, Folder 5376)
    - Thacher School clippings and application, circa 1913 (Box 416, Folder 5377)
    - World War I related clippings, circa 1918 (Box 416, Folder 5378)
    - Franz Kneisel notes, 1962–1978 (Box 416, Folder 5379)
    - Clippings, circa 1922 (Box 417, Folder 5380)
    - Family correspondence, notes, and clippings (13 out of 24 folders), circa 1924-1980 (Box 417, Folder 5381-5394)
    - Clippings, 1998 (Box 427, Folder 5656)
  - Charlotte Wilder
    - Editors' correspondence, 1922–1972 (Box 417, Folder 5395)
    - General correspondence, A-F, 1911–1953 (Box 417, Folder 5396)
    - Publication correspondence (folder 2 of 2), 1921–1950 (Box 417, Folder 5397)
    - Wilder, Amos Parker (folder 1 of 3), 1910–1935 (Box 417, Folder 5398)
    - Wilder family (folder 7 of 7), 1911–1974 (Box 417, Folder 5399)
      Also includes report cards from the China Inland Girls' School, Claremont High School, and Berkeley High School. Also includes New Haven Probate Court documentation of Amos Parker's death.
    - Wilder, Isabel (3 folders out of 11), 1926–1970 (Box 417, Folder 5400-5402)
    - Wilder, Isabella (folder 5 of 13), 1913–1956 (Box 417, Folder 5403-5407)
    - Wilder, Thornton clippings (2 folders), 1975 (Box 417, Folder 5408-5409)
  - Isabel Wilder
    - Writing career materials
      - Clippings (2 folders), 1934, and 1987-1990 (Box 417, Folder 5410-5411)
      - Mother and Four and other materials, 1940–1953 (Box 417, Folder 5412)
      - Coward McCann correspondence, 1932–1941 (Box 417, Folder 5413)
      - Mother and Four duplicate clippings, 1933 (Box 417, Folder 5414)
      - Mother and Four review clippings, 1933 (Box 417, Folder 5415)
      - Dakin, Janet Wilder, 1978–1982 (Box 417, Folder 5416)
        Includes an autobiographical account, clippings, and a letter to Isabella Wilder.
      - Wilder, Thornton clippings, 1977 (Box 417, Folder 5417)
      - Wilder, Thornton materials (1 of 3 folders), circa 1978-1983 (Box 417, Folder 5418-5419)
      - Review clippings and correspondence saved by Catharine Dix Wilder (1 of 2 folders), 1978 (Box 417, Folder 5420-5421)
      - Wilder, Amos Niven materials, 1942–1946 (Box 417, Folder 5422)
      - Thornton Wilder: An Intimate Portrait reviews, 1975 (Box 417, Folder 5423)
        Includes clippings and correspondence relating to Richard Goldstone's biography of Thornton Wilder.
      - Dakin, Janet Wilder materials (folder 1 of 3), 1973–1984 (Box 417, Folder 5424)
      - Dakin, Janet Wilder materials, 1923–1986 (Box 417, Folder 5425)
      - Hobson, Wilder clippings, 1962–1964 (Box 417, Folder 5426)
      - Wilder, Isabella materials (1 of 2 folders), 1931–1938 (Box 417, Folder 5427)
      - Wilder, Amos Niven materials (1 of folders), 1955–1993 (Box 417, Folder 5428)
      - Sculptures, circa 1994 (Box 417, Folder 5429)
      - Wilder family photographs and clippings, 1967–1976 (Box 417, Folder 5430)
      - Wilder, Isabel memorial clippings and program, 1995 (Box 417, Folder 5431)
      - Miscellaneous clippings, 1930–1978 (Box 417, Folder 5432)
      - Wilder, Thornton clippings and notes, undated (Box 417, Folder 5433)
      - Brandt, Carol correspondence and clippings, 1979 (Box 417, Folder 5434)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence (1 of 2 folders), 1942–1993 (Box 418, Folder 5435)
      - Wilder, Thornton memorial service benediction and prayers, 1975–1976 (Box 418, Folder 5436)
      - Wilder, Thornton appraisals, 1970–1978 (Box 418, Folder 5437)
      - The Journals of Thornton Wilder photocopied articles and clippings (1 of 2 folders), 1985 (Box 418, Folder 5438)
      - Wilder, Wilder program and clippings, 1978 (Box 418, Folder 5439)
      - Snow, Emma Folger correspondence and clippings, 1979–1982 (Box 418, Folder 5440)
      - MacDowell Colony correspondence, clippings, and brochures, 1973–1992 (Box 418, Folder 5441)
      - Yale in China materials, 1976–1983 (Box 418, Folder 5442)
      - Thornton Wilder Journals clippings and correspondence, 1985 (Box 418, Folder 5443)
      - Wilder, Thornton clippings (includes 6 of 6 folders), 1926–1986 (Box 418, Folder 5444-5449)
      - Wilder, Wilder program, clippings, and correspondence (1 of 2 folders), 1978–1979 (Box 418, Folder 5450)
      - The Skin of Our Teeth programs and photocopied articles, 1975–1993 (Box 418, Folder 5451)
      - Harrison, Gilbert correspondence and clippings, 1938 (Box 418, Folder 5452)
      - The Enthusiast: A Life of Thornton Wilder clippings and promotional material (3 of 4 folders), 1983 (Box 418, Folder 5453-5455)
      - Wilder, Thornton The Alcestiad clippings and reviews (2 folders), 1976–1978 (Box 418, Folder 5456-5457)
      - The Journals of Thornton Wilder clippings, 1985 (Box 418, Folder 5458)
      - Hello Dolly clipping and photographs, 1979–1990 (Box 418, Folder 5459)
      - Shadow of a Doubt clipping, undated (Box 418, Folder 5460)
      - Our Town, musical version, clippings and photocopy typescript fragments, 1987–1990 (Box 418, Folder 5461)
      - Our Town clippings (2 of 4 folders), 1987–1990 (Box 418, Folder 5462-5463)
      - Movie adaptations clippings, 1968–1982 (Box 418, Folder 5464)
      - Wilder, Wilder, Wilder program and clippings (2 of 2 folders), 1993 (Box 418, Folder 5465-5466)
      - Wilder, Thornton bust and study unveilings clippings, 1983–1986 (Box 418, Folder 5467)
      - Wilder, Thornton clippings (3 of 3 folders), 1977, 1984-1989 (Box 418, Folder 5468-5470)
        Includes one article in French.
      - Madison, Wisconsin clippings, 1977 (Box 418, Folder 5471)
      - A Celebration of Thornton Wilder at the Circle in the Square Theatre photocopied clippings and program, 1977 (Box 418, Folder 5472)
      - Great Lakes Shakespeare Festival and related clippings, 1984–1990 (Box 418, Folder 5473)
      - Thornton Wilder at the Hamden Public Library materials (1 of 3 folders), 1975–1987 (Box 418, Folder 5474)
      - Hamden Bicentennial Commission (1 of 2 folders), 1975–1983 (Box 418, Folder 5475)
      - Thornton Wilder Memorial correspondence and clippings (1 of 2 folders), 1979–1990 (Box 418, Folder 5476)
      - The Thornton Wilder Writing Competition at the Hamden Public Library materials (1 of 2 folders), 1989–1991 (Box 418, Folder 5477)
      - Berkeley house fire clipping, 1974 November 6 (Box 418, Folder 5478)
      - Dakin, Janet Wilder correspondence and clippings, 1927–1971 (Box 418, Folder 5479)
      - Week of Authors programs and clippings, 1933-1934, 1960 (Box 418, Folder 5480)
      - The Skin of Our Teeth televised production clippings and correspondence, 1982–1986 (Box 418, Folder 5481)
      - Gallup, Donald correspondence, clippings, and photocopied articles (1 of 3 folders), 1952–1994 (Box 418, Folder 5482)
      - Hutchins, Robert Maynard correspondence, clippings, and memorial service program, 1933–1977 (Box 418, Folder 5483)
      - La Follette, Robert M. clippings, photocopied articles, and literature review, 1953 (Box 418, Folder 5484)
      - Partridge, Eric correspondence, clippings, and printed Christmas and New Year's Greetings, 1959–1977 (Box 418, Folder 5485)
      - Dakin, Janet Wilder correspondence (1 of 8 folders), 1931–1987 (Box 418, Folder 5486)
      - Wilder, Charlotte condolence letters and clippings, circa 1980 (Box 419, Folder 5487)
      - Handwritten fragments and clippings, 1936 (Box 419, Folder 5488)
      - Downs, Arthur correspondence and clippings, 1969–1972 (Box 419, Folder 5489)
      - Wilder, Hobson and family correspondence and clippings (1 of 2 folders), 1909–1970 (Box 419, Folder 5490)
      - Wilder, Isabella material, 1928–1946 (Box 419, Folder 5491)
      - Clippings, 1992–1993 (Box 419, Folder 5492)
      - Photocopied Thornton Wilder correspondence and correspondence fragments, 1963–1970 (Box 419, Folder 5493)
        Also includes Mother of Four clippings and photocopied Thacher School articles.
  - Janet Wilder Dakin
    - Janet Wilder Dakin materials (2 folders) (Box 419, Folder 5494-5495)
  - Wilder family papers
    - Wilder, Amos Parker clippings, 1921–1956 (Box 419, Folder 5496-5497)
    - Wilder, Isabella Emile Verhaeren reviews and review correspondence, 1914 (Box 419, Folder 5498)
    - Wilder, Isabella poetry, clippings, and correspondence fragments, 1902–1916 (Box 419, Folder 5499)
    - Wilder, Isabella personal papers, 1916–1946 (Box 419, Folder 5500)
    - Clippings, 1928–1936 (Box 427, Folder 5657)
    - Clippings, 1928 (Box 427, Folder 5658)
    - Scrapbook enclosures, 1957–1968 (Box 427, Folder 5659-5660)
    - Programs saved by Tappan Wilder, 1914–2012
      - Olla Prodrida from Berkeley High School and enclosures, 1914 June–1915 (Box 419, Folder 5501)
      - Our Town Lincoln Center production, clippings, correspondence, 1988–1989 (Box 419, Folder 5502)
      - Grover's Corners materials (1 of 2 folders), 1987–2006 (Box 419, Folder 5503)
      - Our Town Madison Repertory Theatre production clippings and programs, 2006 (Box 419, Folder 5504)
      - Our Town Westport production clippings, reviews, programs, and photocopied reviews, 2002 (Box 419, Folder 5505)
      - Our Town Masterpiece Theatre television production materials (1 of 2 folders), 2003 (Box 419, Folder 5506)
    - Hello Dolly materials
      - Stage correspondence, clippings, and agreements, 1966–1972 (Box 419, Folder 5507)
  - Freedman contracts
    - The Skin of Our Teeth materials (1 of 2 folders), 1971–1975 (Box 419, Folder 5508)
    - Our Town materials (folder 1 of 3), 1982–1988 (Box 419, Folder 5509)
    - Our Town materials: Anglo- American and Shafetesbury productions (1 of 2 folders), 1991–1992 (Box 419, Folder 5510)
    - Heaven's My Destination materials (folder 2 of 3), 1957–1977 (Box 419, Folder 5511)
    - Our Town materials (folder 1 of 3), 1960–1963 (Box 419, Folder 5512)
    - Our Town materials (folder 1 of 2), 1941–1954 (Box 419, Folder 5513)
    - Our Town materials (folders 1 and 2 of 3), 1964–1967 (Box 419, Folder 5514-5515)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth materials, 1967–1968 (Box 419, Folder 5516)
    - Theophilius North film with Haft Entertainment materials, 1984–1988 (Box 419, Folder 5517)
    - General correspondence (14 out of 15 folders), 1932–1955 (Box 419, Folder 5518-5523, Box 420, Folder 5524-5531)
    - The Matchmaker correspondence (8 out of 11 folders), 1954–1955 (Box 420, Folder 5532-5539)
    - Our Town Italian stage and television productions correspondence (folder 2 of 2), 1967–1975 (Box 420, Folder 5540)
    - General correspondence (10 out of 21 folders), 1950–1977 (Box 420, Folder 5541-5550)
    - Our Town correspondence (folders 2 and 3 of 3), 1969–1976 (Box 420, Folder 5551-5552)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth correspondence (3 of 12 folders), 1942–1967 (Box 420, Folder 5553-5555)
    - The Eighth Day correspondence (folder 2 of 6), 1966–1992 (Box 420, Folder 5556)
    - Our Town correspondence (folder 2 of 9), 1989–1995 (Box 420, Folder 5557)
    - Our Town television production correspondence, contracts, and notes (folder 2 of 3), 1973–1986 (Box 420, Folder 5558)
    - Our Town correspondence, agreements, and notes (folders 2 of 3), 1951–1972 (Box 420, Folder 5559-5560)
    - The Ides of March correspondence, agreements, contracts, and notes (folder 3 of 3), 1967–1992 (Box 420, Folder 5561)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth correspondence, agreements, and notes, clippings and notes (6 of 9 folders), 1944–1978 (Box 420, Folder 5562-5567)
    - The Matchmaker correspondence and notes (folder 2 of 2), 1964–1975 (Box 420, Folder 5568)
    - Hello Dolly correspondence (folder 1 of 2), 1963 May–1964 (Box 420, Folder 5569)
    - Hello Dolly correspondence (folder 2 of 2), 1964 June–1972 (Box 421, Folder 5570-5571)
    - Infancy and Childhood correspondence (folder 2 of 2), 1965–1975 (Box 421, Folder 5572)
    - General correspondence (folders 1 and 2 of 2), 1946–1947 (Box 421, Folder 5573-5574)
    - Spanish and Portuguese translation correspondence (folder 1 of 2), 1962–1967 (Box 421, Folder 5575)
    - Plumstead Playhouse Our Town correspondence (folder 1 of 2), 1968–1973 (Box 421, Folder 5576)
    - General correspondence (folders 1 and 2 of 8), 1954–1985 (Box 421, Folder 5577-5578)
    - Our Town correspondence (folder 1 of 3), 1983–1989 (Box 421, Folder 5579)
    - General correspondence, agreements, and The Matchmaker photocopied reviews (folder 2 of 2), 1992–1993 (Box 421, Folder 5580)
  - Wiggin and Dana
    - Charlotte Wilder materials
      - Mental illness notes, correspondence, and clippings, 1939–2008 (Box 421, Folder 5581)
        Includes notes and correspondence, both handwritten and photocopied, among family membres including Amos Niven Wilder about Charlotte's mental illness. Also includes typescript chronologies, and newspaper articles.
      - " After Anger " poetry clipping, 1935 (Box 421, Folder 5582)
      - Fragments, undated (Box 421, Folder 5583)
    - Amos N. Wilder materials
      - Lewis, Wilmarth "Lefty" S. correspondence and clippings, 1969–1979 (Box 421, Folder 5584)
      - Yu, Anthony correspondence and clippings, 1978–1983 (Box 421, Folder 5585)
      - Honors and special events clippings, lists, and correspondence (2 of 2 folders), 1965–1993 (Box 421, Folder 5586-5587)
      - Wilder-Niven family biography notes, circa 1976 (Box 421, Folder 5588)
      - Biographical materials (2 of 2 folders), 1911–1986 (Box 421, Folder 5589-5590)
      - Memorial service materials (folder 2 of 2), circa 1993 (Box 421, Folder 5591)
      - Obituary clippings, photocopied clippings, typescript and correspondence (folder 2 of 2), 1993–1994 (Box 421, Folder 5592)
      - WWI related clippings and correspondence, 1999 (Box 421, Folder 5593)
      - Clippings and correspondence, 1971–1986 (Box 421, Folder 5594)
      - Notes, clippings, and correspondence, 1911–1986 (Box 421, Folder 5595)
      - Certificates, clippings, programs and match sheets (folders 2 of 2), 1915–1989 (Box 421, Folder 5596-5597)
      - Programs, clippings, correspondence, and notes, 1930–1986 (Box 421, Folder 5598)
      - Clippings, correspondence, and notes, 1914–1988 (Box 421, Folder 5599)
      - Continent related clippings and ephemera from Pau, Brussels, and Geneva, 1924–1929 (Box 421, Folder 5600)
      - New England lawn tennis ephemera, clippings, and correspondence, 1924–1928 (Box 421, Folder 5601)
      - Wimbledon clippings and correspondence, 1986 (Box 421, Folder 5602)
      - Oxford correspondence and notes, 1973–1975 (Box 421, Folder 5603)
      - The Oberlin Reviews and clippings, circa 1915 (Box 421, Folder 5604)
      - Yale lawn tennis clippings, correspondence, and ephemera, 1920–1986 (Box 421, Folder 5605)
      - Photographs, correspondence, and clippings, 1913–1990 (Box 421, Folder 5606)
      - American Field Service photocopied and original research, clippings, and ephemera (2 of 3 folders), 1974–1992 (Box 421, Folder 5607-5608)
      - Wilder, Amos Parker correspondence, 1916–1926 (Box 421, Folder 5609)
      - Background research clippings and articles for Armageddon Revisited, 1981–2004 (Box 421, Folder 5610)
      - Valdahon camp clippings, 1917–1918 (Box 421, Folder 5611)
      - Wilder records, correspondence, and clippings, 1918–1971 (Box 422, Folder 5612)
      - Clippings, 1918 January (Box 422, Folder 5613)
      - Clippings, 1917 December–1918 January (Box 422, Folder 5614)
      - Handwritten and photocopied correpondence, clippings, and miscellaneous correspondence, 1917 (Box 422, Folder 5615)
      - Wilder records, clippings, and correspondence, 1919 (Box 422, Folder 5616)
      - Clippings and typescript writings, 1918 (Box 422, Folder 5617)
      - Typescript notes and clippings, 1918 (Box 422, Folder 5618)
      - Clippings, 1918 (Box 422, Folder 5619)
      - Clippings, 1917 (Box 422, Folder 5620)
      - Clipping, undated (Box 422, Folder 5621)
      - Biographical notes, correspondence, and clippings, 2002–2008 (Box 422, Folder 5622)
      - Obituary related correspondence and clippings, 1995 (Box 422, Folder 5623)
    - Janet Wilder Dakin materials
      - Conservation efforts correspondence, clippings, and photographs, 1978–2003 (Box 422, Folder 5624)
      - Janet and Toby Dakin clippings, correspondence, and ephemera, 1938–1983 (Box 422, Folder 5625)
      - Memorial and internment materials, circa 1994 (Box 422, Folder 5626)
  - Musical works based on Thornton Wilder's plays, 1961–2008
    - Grover's Corners clippings and programs, 1977–1987 (Box 422, Folder 5627)
    - Musical clippings, programs, and scripts, 2005–2007 (Box 422, Folder 5628)
    - Paul Hindemith photocopied correspondence, undated (Box 422, Folder 5629)
    - Music notes, clippings, and photocopied correspondence, circa 2002 (Box 422, Folder 5630)
  - Wiggin and Dana materials
    - The Skin of Our Teeth materials (Box 422, Folder 5631)
    - Documents, general (folder 1 of 2), 1942–1967 (Box 422, Folder 5632)
    - Wilder, Estate of Isabel estate administration
      - Documents, 1966–1995 (Box 422, Folder 5633)
    - Grover's Corners materials
      - Photocopied agreements, correspondence, clippings, and notes (1 of 4 folders), 1986–1987 (Box 422, Folder 5634)
      - Film and television correspondence (folder 1 of 2), 1954–1998 (Box 422, Folder 5635)
      - Film contracts and related materials (folder 1 of 3), 1980–1984 (Box 422, Folder 5636)
      - Thornton Wilder postage stamp and centennial celebration materials (folder 1 of 3), 1996–1997 (Box 422, Folder 5637)
      - Thornton Wilder postage stamp materials (folders 1, 2, and of 4), 1995–2007 (Box 422, Folder 5638-5640)